A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Education and Research Division, Office Files of Fred E. Crossland FA713
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Correspondence Files, 1972-1979; II
  - Chronological Files, B
    - DEC, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 588)
    - NOV, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 589)
    - OCT, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 590)
    - SEP, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 591)
    - AUG, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 592)
    - JUL, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 593)
    - JUN, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 594)
    - MAY, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 595)
    - APR, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 596)
    - MAR, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 597)
    - FEB, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 598)
    - JAN, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 599)
    - DEC, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 600)
    - NOV, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 601)
    - OCT, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 602)
    - SEP, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 603)
    - AUG, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 604)
    - JUL, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 605)
    - JUN, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 606)
    - MAY, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 607)
    - APR, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 608)
    - MAR, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 609)
    - FEB, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 610)
    - JAN, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 611)
  - Inter-Office Memoranda, C
    These files consist of Crossland's selected outgoing correspondence with Ford Foundation colleagues and memos to the "File." Within each folder, the correspondence is arranged in reverse calendar order.
    - JUN, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 612)
    - MAY, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 613)
    - APR, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 614)
    - MAR, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 615)
    - FEB, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 616)
    - JAN, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 617)
    - DEC, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 618)
    - NOV, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 619)
    - OCT, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 620)
    - SEP, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 621)
    - AUG, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 622)
    - JUL, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 623)
    - JUN, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 624)
    - MAY, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 625)
    - APR, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 626)
    - MAR, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 627)
    - FEB, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 628)
    - JAN, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 629)